The Dragon's Fang has been stolen?
How horrifying.
Worry not, Your Majesty.
I already have a force
in pursuit of the thief.
(That Time I Got Reincarnated as a Slime
the Movie: Tears of the Azure Sea)
My name is Mikami Satoru—
rather, Rimuru Tempest.
I used to be an ordinary human,
and a salaryman working
for a major general contracting firm...
until I was stabbed to death.
And as you can see,
I've reincarnated as a slime.
But I knew there'd be no point
in wondering how it happened,
so I tried to just enjoy my
slime life in my own way, and...
Before I knew it, I had lots of friends,
and then I built an entire
monster nation called Tempest
and became its king.
Of course, I had to deal
with some interference
from people who didn't like that...
but I overcame the difficulties
and finally became a Demon Lord.
And then Tempest held
its opening festival.
I want to dream big
and build a world where everyone
could enjoy living together,
and my friends and I are still
working hard to achieve that.
And right now, we're on our way
to Elmesia-san's resort to celebrate
the success of our festival.
Wow!
I had no idea traveling
by dragon airship was so comfortable.
I didn't know a journey
could be so relaxing.
Reading manga in the sky is great!
And all the booze is choice!
And all the snacks are tasty!
Okay, you guys are a little too relaxed.
I appreciate you inviting us, as well.
I'm glad you all seem
to be enjoying the ride.
Elmesia-san, thank you
for inviting us on this trip.
Yes, we're grateful
for everything you're doing.
Oh, this is nothing at all.
That said, you are truly
a wonderful ruler,
arranging a pleasure trip like this.
I envy your subjects.
Oh, not at all.
I just wanted to cut loose a little.
You said we're going to your resort.
What do you have there?
Well, let's see...
It has a market and a harbor.
And it's a tourist resort,
so I think you'll find it enjoyable.
Great Rimuru! I can see the resort!
How lovely!
It's even more impressive than I imagined.
Isn't this exciting, Great Rimuru?
Yeah.
C'mon, hurry!
Wait up!
A dragon airship!
Cool!
Let's go!
We have awaited your
arrival, Lady Elmesia.
Great Rimuru, if there is
anything you require, please ask.
It's good to meet you, too.
When I see it from here,
that dragon really is huge.
Notice.
That is the Guardian Dragon King.
It is most likely
a type of Elemental Dragon.
An Elemental Dragon?
That's right. I'm impressed you knew.
Wait, it really is?
So I guess Milim's pet dragon that was
killed by a human wasn't the only one.
Indeed, a few others do exist.
But they rarely show themselves,
so they are regarded as legends.
My first time at a resort!
I can't help hoping
I'll meet someone amazing!
This is the entrance to the town.
Please enjoy yourselves
however you please.
Thank you for bringing us here.
I see food stalls!
What?! Food stalls?!
I know where I'm headed!
Hold it, Milim! Don't leave me behind!
Zoom!
Goodness. No patience at all.
Sorry about them, Elmesia-san.
Oh, it's all right.
What are you doing after this?
I have some special liquor set aside.
I'll be enjoying that.
Liquor?!
I'm going, too!
I wanna try this special stuff of yours!
What drink could earn such favor
from the Heavenly Empress?
What do you think?
I think we can expect something excellent.
Well, we have nothing better to do.
We will be joining you, as well.
Oh, my!
Uh-huh! Uh-huh!
Very well, then! Let's all drink!
Damn right I'm drinking!
They're too free-spirited.
Great Rimuru.
We will go and inspect the island.
"Inspect," eh?
Yeah, sure. Go ahead.
Can't wait to see what you catch.
Sir!
So this is how liberating
resorts can be...
Great Rimuru!
I wanna go see the ocean!
- That sounds great!
- I'd love to go!
The ocean, huh?
You're right. We're here
on vacation, after all.
We're gonna enjoy the hell out of it!
Yeah!
You're gonna be so surprised!
The ocean here is just beautiful!
All of Thalion's top elites
and their guests come here
in huge parties on vacation.
Have you been here before, Eren?
Yeah! El brought me!
I wish the others could've come with us.
We'll have to let everyone who couldn't
come this time have their turns here.
There's no need
for the second secretary to come.
To leave your side would be unthinkable!
He clearly lacks the mentality
to be a secretary!
Do you want him to come or don't you?
Where do you suppose Diablo is right now?
You want a subordinate?
Yes.
I would like a subordinate
to whom I can entrust miscellaneous tasks.
Like preparing tea?
Ah, no! Not for that!
Taking care of you
is very important work for me.
That is not why.
I would like a subordinate I can send
on miscellaneous errands such as
destroying other nations and the like.
Does this guy hear himself?
I have an old acquaintance
who may be ideal for the role.
That is who I would like
to go and recruit.
Would you grant me permission?
I allowed it, and Diablo
took off somewhere... but...
I'm worried.
Just who is he going to bring back?
Great Rimuru!
Enough about that! Look ahead!
It's the ocean!
It's huge!
It's amazing!
This is such a nice place.
Isn't it?
So nice.
Yeah, this really is a great place!
It is!
Great Rimuru!
Won't you come and join us?
The water's great!
Sure! On my way!
Rimuru Tempest...
Take that!
Oh, Great Rimuru!
That's not enough!
Take that!
Oh, now you've done it!
Over here!
Great Rimuru? What is it?
What could that be?
This is the best!
Please, Lady Ramiris, control yourself.
Oh, it's fine!
Where'd that thing come from?
Don't care.
That light...
Notice.
It appears to be nuclear magic.
It does not affect this island.
I see...
I must hurry!
Attack incoming!
Send an emergency alert
throughout the country!
All of you, cover your heads!
What in the world was that?
Notice. In addition to
a nuclear magic impact,
I have confirmed a vibration
reverberating in another location.
Another location?
So, just as the rumors said...
Ol' Leon sure has it rough.
Leon? You mean Demon Lord Leon Cromwell?
Yes.
Why bring up Demon Lord Leon?
A part of his domain, the Golden
City of El Dorado, is near here,
and it seems like someone's
trying to mess with it!
Mess with it?
Demon Lord Leon's been using
a protective barrier
to reflect the nuclear magic
attacks it's occasionally hit with.
Well, someone's sure causing
a lot of trouble, huh?
Are the people of this
island gonna be okay?
I have heard that there is
no need for concern.
The attacks land in the open sea,
too far away to affect the island.
Leon has been very careful
about that, it seems.
The people on the island
are used to it, apparently.
Huh...
What's for dinner tonight?
Well, that's good, I guess...
but who would mess with a Demon Lord?
All wasted efforts.
Does that demon never tire of these games?
The people have come to regard it
as a feature of the season.
It is very troubling indeed.
Djeese! Where is Djeese?!
Right here.
Oh, Djeese!
If nothing is done, this nation will fall!
Hasn't the Great Water
Dragon awakened yet?
The search for the stolen
Dragon's Fang is still underway.
What are they doing?!
We need the Great Water
Dragon's power right now!
I have dispatched Zodon.
Please wait a bit longer.
They're selling all kinds of things.
What should we buy
to take home to the others?
What do you think?
Hard to choose, isn't it?
Oh, how cute!
Why don't we go with this?
It's cute!
Wow, that's really well-made.
This stuff's handmade
by the people of this island.
So this is an income source for them.
They sell cute hair
accessories over there, too!
It doesn't even matter
what we buy for those guys.
That attitude is unacceptable!
Let's go, Gobta.
Fine...
Wait! Wait! Wait, little lady!
You've come to the right place!
Here! Act now,
and I'll throw this in, too!
Lord Djeese, I've found her.
Moving in.
Good. Don't disappoint me.
Of course.
Where'd he go?
Hold it.
You got business with Great Rimuru?
I'm sorry. I don't know what you mean.
It's no use trying to play dumb.
You've been...
following us this whole time, haven't you?
I think you've mistaken me
for someone else.
Excuse me! Let me through!
I can't let someone
as shady as you get past me.
Who are you calling shady?
I'm the daughter of one of
the fishermen here.
Wh-What does the daughter
of a fisherman want with us?
My point is that I couldn't
care less about you lot.
Wh-Why don't you just tell
the truth already?!
Right, Great Rimuru?
Huh?
He's gone...
Great Rimuru is gone!
Wait... That's bad!
Hey! What're you gonna do now?!
What else? I have to look for him!
- Great Rimuru!
- Huh?
Hey! Don't take off on your own!
Soon... Soon, now...
How long are you gonna follow me?
We just happen to be going the same way.
Oh, I see.
What?
Nothing.
What's wrong? You can go on ahead.
What is this creature?
You're so cute! You're so cute!
And so soft!
Don't leave without me.
You tell me to walk,
then you tell me not to leave.
Talk about unreasonable.
More importantly, is this the right way?
I don't know.
You're from this island.
Why don't you know?
You know, I was thinking...
I bet your master's forgotten about you.
You don't seem all that special.
I am one of Tempest's Elite Four!
The name's Gobta!
Elite Four?
That's right.
So there's no way he'd forget about me.
I'm sure Great Rimuru's looking
for me right now!
We should be able to spot him from here.
Okay! Next is a very special activity:
a limestone cave tour!
That sounds fun!
Indeed!
Welcome to the limestone cave tour!
How many in your party?
Four!
Looks like he did forget about you.
Great Rimuru...
Oh, no! We'll lose sight of him again!
We gotta hurry!
Hey, wait!
It's so pretty.
It feels very calming.
Feels like another world, huh?
The legends say
any couple who reach this cave's
exit together will be together forever!
Welcome to the limestone cave tour!
How many in your party?
- One!
So... two, then?
Enjoy!
Wasn't the cave beautiful, Great Rimuru?
That was fun!
Great Rimuru, let's make
one of those in Tempest!
We're going after him at full speed!
This way! I know he went this way!
- Let's go!
- Dash!
Great Rimuru!
Hey! You keep getting in my way!
I can't help it! This thing's tiny!
You should have waited for the next seal.
I can't let you get ahead of me!
I've had enough of you talking down to me!
I'm Yura! Don't forget it!
I'm Gobta.
Wow, limestone cave donuts, huh?
Oh, yeah! Ranga!
Sir!
Want another?
Don't be shy! Eat up!
I am truly grateful!
We really have lost him.
- Something just—
- Hey!
Where do you think you're touching?!
- I-I didn't—
- What's your deal, you pervert?!
You could not be more mistaken!
Be quiet!
Who do you think I—
Ow...
You okay?
Oh, you probably shouldn't move.
You're not hurt, are you?
I thought you found me suspicious.
Why did you help me?
I dunno.
You don't need a reason to help someone.
Well, let's go find the exit.
I was just fine on my own.
Still, I'm glad you're not hurt.
I'm never coming here again.
Well?
I haven't captured her yet.
Are you that incompetent?
What are you doing?!
I'm sorry.
All I need is the flute.
Just bring it back at once!
As you wish.
It feels like we've wandered
into another world.
This area is made like
a maze, so be careful.
- How exciting! It's like a labyrinth!
- A labyrinth...
Challenge accepted.
There aren't gonna be any enemies.
Great Rimuru, the path splits up here.
Okay! We'll go left!
Finding out what awaits on the path ahead
is one of the best parts of traveling.
Great Rimuru! Where are you?
For crying out loud...
We don't even have a clue
which way he went.
So...
is that "Elite Four" thing true?
Sure is!
I'm one of the top brass!
Wow. You're pretty impressive, then.
Which way?
When you're lost... go right!
Are you sure?
Hey, are you even listening?
You know the task.
Feel free to be a little rough with her.
Yes, sir!
Yura?
They've already made it this far?
Gobta!
You noticed, too?
Why are they chasing us?
Let her go!
You okay?
I got careless!
Gobta.
You saved my skin!
You're pretty impressive yourself!
Those guys just don't know when to quit!
Why are they chasing us?!
What?!
Behave yourself, and no one gets hurt.
Yura!
Zodon!
Damn it! She's gone!
We lost her?
I know "pretty," I know "lovely,"
yet nothing ever truly begins, just easy days
Even when my heart beats a little faster
My thoughts drift to the darker side first
And yet, somehow, today again
I'm enjoying a day that isn't ordinary
People change... no, it's me who's changed
So this must be
That thing everyone talks about?
It's actually kind of nice
Because
"It's okay to want to see you as much as I do."
Even when I'm with you, I still want you more
The "No" I said without thinking
will change by tomorrow
And
"If I want to see you, I can just go see you."
When it really matters, I wish I had more time
Ah
You've only just settled into the center of me
I don't plan to move you anytime soon
Not many things can
make me moan this much...
Very impressive, I must say.
Oh, my.
Can you really tell the difference?
What does that mean?!
If you're pickin' a fight, bring it on!
Lady Ramiris...
Lady Frey is over there.
Did it just get noisier around here?
Did it?
Indeed. It made me curious, as well.
I didn't notice.
You fools! That's obviously nuclear magic!
Oh, right. That happens around here.
In that case, there's no need to worry.
Lady Ramiris, what would
you like to drink next?
Oh, let's see...
Lady Ramiris, perhaps you should stop...
This should be far enough...
I never knew it looked this amazing.
It's beautiful.
Sure is.
So this is what a real sunset looks like.
I wonder why it's so red.
I could look at this forever.
You said it.
Huh?
I've never really looked
at the sky like this for long, either.
We've always had our hands full just
dealing with what's right in front of us.
There's never any time
to take in the scenery.
I see.
But if I'd just looked up,
I would've seen this awesome view.
I guess I've taken another step
toward becoming a bigger man!
Huh?
Well, well.
So sorry to interrupt this lovely mood.
They got this far?!
Lady Yura, you must return to our kingdom.
- Gobta, over here!
- Huh?
- Over here!
- N-No way! I can't!
What?!
Gobta!
Yura!
Yura?!
Yura! Can you hear me?!
- Yura!
- Calm down.
She's only unconscious.
Let's just take her
someplace safe for now.
Gobta, you should rest, too.
Great Rimuru...
Don't worry. She'll wake up soon.
I... guess so.
Denizens of the sea
To nurture your hopes and dreams
Your small bodies huddle together
As you swim among the waves
Within the circling whirlpool
Tears and sea foam dissolve
The light of life
Becomes the starry sky
Guiding you to your destination
On the endless path you travel
Time and azure, ever flowing,
Carry with them new encounters
A voice rings through the ages, unceasing
Singing a song of peace and wishes
To all awakening from their slumber
To one and all...
Great...
...gon.
Here it is.
Well done, Zodon.
Begin the preparations at once.
Of course.
As you wish.
Do your job flawlessly next time.
Yes, sir.
How was she?
Still sleeping.
I see.
Where is Djeese?
Isn't the Great Water Dragon awake yet?
I am here.
Oh, Djeese!
Where is Yura?
And the Dragon's Fang?
What of the Great Water Dragon?
I have recovered the
Dragon's Fang from her.
I have it right here.
That's my Djeese!
Oh, but I thought only
a priestess could use that...
The analysis is complete.
For me, this mechanism
is mere child's play.
Notice. That is nuclear magic.
This is surely a sign!
I will now use this flute to put
the Great Water Dragon to work!
Behold!
What... was that?
Oh, no! Veldora!
I'm on it!
Destroy!
So what's next?
What's the matter? Off to sulk
because I'm too strong?
What was that?
It looked like a dragon...
Yura!
My name is Yura.
I am a priestess of the nation of Kaien.
A priestess?
Kaien?
Isn't that the nation at the bottom of
the sea? From the island's fairy tales?
I believe this island was friendly
with them once, long ago...
Does this have anything to do
with that dragon?
That dragon is the Water Dragon,
Kaien's guardian deity.
Someone awakened it in a bid
to launch an attack on the surface.
The surface?!
Come to think of it,
Kaien's chancellor is Djeese...
is it not?
Um... Are you...
I'm Elmesia El-Ru Thalion.
The Holy Empress?!
More importantly...
There is more, is there not?
Y-Yes.
It seems I lack the strength
to stop Djeese on my own.
I came up to the surface to seek help,
and things there got even worse...
Great Rimuru, please! I want to help Yura!
I want to do something!
This is all a bit sudden, though...
In that case, I myself will make
a formal request.
Would you please go to Kaien
and resolve the situation?
Uh...
Don't tell me...
that the reason you invited us here was...
Whatever do you mean?
But you know, there is nothing more
expensive than something given for free.
Okay. We'll go to the bottom of the ocean.
To Kaien!
We'll help you, Yura-san!
Thank you so much.
Rimuru!
Why are you leaving me behind?
Veldora-kun...
Only the strongest guy around can
protect this place from nuclear magic.
Oho...
- The strongest?
- Yes!
And who's the strongest?
You, Veldora-kun!
You're the only one
I can entrust this place to!
Well, then, I have no choice!
Because I am the strongest, after all!
Well, shall we go?
- I want you to stay here, too.
- Huh?
I wanna go with you!
- With you!
- Milim...
Oh, what a shame.
They have such delicious
sweets made by Mr. Yoshida here.
Really?!
Let's eat some together.
I'm in!
As am I, of course!
Good, that's settled.
Man, I couldn't be more
grateful to Frey-san.
If I brought those two along,
they'd destroy whole cities.
So just what is this Water Dragon?
My ancestors once lived on the surface.
But...
they hated conflict, so they set off
to wander in search of a land
where they could live in peace.
It was the Great Water Dragon
and its messenger that gave them
a kingdom at the bottom of the ocean.
The Great Water Dragon then fell
into a very long slumber,
and my clan received the flute.
A flute that allows you to
establish a soul connection with
the Great Water Dragon, yes?
Yes.
We have lived in peace ever since then.
But then, a few decades ago,
things changed.
The nuclear magic.
It has been causing destruction
in Kaien on a daily basis.
We heard the strikes
were landing far away.
But they're hitting Kaien?
But I'd think ol' Leon would do
something to prevent any harm.
It seems Djeese was behind all of it.
The nuclear magic strikes themselves
were landing in locations
where they didn't affect Kaien.
But then...
Djeese was causing separate
explosions closer to the kingdom
to make everyone think they
were harming Kaien.
Come to think of it, Raphael did say...
Notice. In addition to
a nuclear magic impact,
I have confirmed a vibration
reverberating in another location.
So that's what that meant?
Djeese is the chancellor of Kaien, right?
He's been called the greatest genius
known to Kaien since its founding.
He has studied the cultures
and civilizations of the surface world
to bring drastic
improvements to our lives.
Well, if you say so,
Djeese, it must be true...
That was a preparatory strike by Demon
Lords who want to invade our nation.
What?!
I suspect we will soon see an
all-out assault by Demon Lord
Rimuru acting as a vanguard.
How can you be so sure?
Because I have taken some of
the Demon Lord's subordinates prisoner.
Speak.
Demon Lord Rimuru said he was
going to "kill them all."
He was launching strikes
at random, trying to find this location.
He will attack soon.
Your Majesty.
I have an idea.
Oh! Djeese?
We only need to awaken
the Great Water Dragon.
Wha—
You can do that?
If I study the ancient texts,
it may be possible.
That's taboo!
Our nation will fall if I don't.
But...
It is for the good of Kaien.
We can't allow this, Lady Yura.
Lady Yura...
Now, your decision, please.
If it will benefit the kingdom, then...
Is there a problem?
Oh, I wouldn't call it a "problem,"
but it seems Demon Lord Rimuru
is coming to a nearby island.
We gonna be okay?
I hear he's soft.
I'm sure everything will work out.
That's our Djeese!
So... about our reward...
Not to worry.
I will, however,
ask you to do one last task.
As long as we get paid!
I see.
But no matter how strong
the Water Dragon is,
waging war on a Demon
Lord seems unrealistic.
No.
We cannot say so for sure.
True.
If this being called the Water Dragon
is what I imagine it is...
it may not be so far-fetched
for it to have such a foolish dream.
That's a nice song.
Oh, this?
It's a song of prayer
to the Great Water Dragon.
I normally play it on a flute.
Gobta...
I'm sorry.
Huh?
I used you.
No, no, no! You didn't have a choice!
And I'm just as guilty for doubting you.
I'm sorry.
You know, the Great Water Dragon's power
exists to protect all
living things in this ocean.
And to use that for war...
Well, you've got me!
And as long as you've got the great
Gobta, there's nothing to worry about!
That's very reassuring.
I have been waiting for you, Lady Yura.
That voice... It's Djeese!
Behold, King Lete.
Just as I told you,
this Priestess of the Water Dragon,
Yura, stole the flute
and is bringing the surface
world's vanguard force here.
She's bringing people
from the surface to Kaien?!
I can't believe Lady Yura would betray us.
Lady Yura would never do that!
Are you saying Lord Djeese is lying?
That's impossible.
Djeese! Show yourself!
The flute!
Notice. Massive energy response coming
from under the sea.
It can't be...
It's the Water Dragon!
Djeese!
I shall slay the traitor Yura
and the invaders' vanguard!
That flute is not for you to possess!
Nonsense.
The idea that only one of the priestess's
clan can play it is mere superstition.
The flute does not need
you for its master.
Although it is still a fact that only one
with sufficient energy can use it.
However...
I myself...
can play it!
Incoming!
Gobta!
Great Rimuru!
Beelzebub!
All of you, stay here!
What do you think of
that incredible power?!
I can't fathom why
we never used it before!
Djeese...
You lot upheld the laws so faithfully
that you never read
the ancient text, didn't you?
It contained records of how
to use it this way, as well...
Damn it... You monster!
Great Water Dragon!
Yura!
Great Rimuru! We should go, too!
Yeah. Let's go!
You saved me!
We need to hurry!
Yes, sir!
Yura!
Yura?
Everything's... fine now.
The flute!
Notice. The Water Dragon has disappeared.
Demon Lord Rimuru, I welcome you.
Thank you.
It's an honor to meet you, King Lete.
I don't know how to apologize
for my kingdom's misconduct.
There's no need to apologize.
I just hope nothing else happens.
What's this?
Oh...
This was drawn when our ancestors
first started living here.
So that's Kaien, and...
are those lines under it water currents?
That's you, isn't it, Yura?
Huh?
No, that's
the scene of the Great Water Dragon
and its messenger giving us the flute.
Er, huh?
You were just trying
to get her attention, huh?
I get it, Gobta-kun. Uh-huh.
But she said the ancestors
drew it, remember?
Oh, yeah...
Guess I jumped to conclusions.
It just looked so much like Yura...
I'm honored.
This is incredible.
It's so well-maintained.
Notice. I surmise that these are ruins.
They appear to have been outfitted
with various facilities.
Lady Yura!
- Lady Yura!
- Welcome back!
I'm so glad you're safe!
I had faith in you all along, Lady Yura!
You and your silver tongue.
- Lady Yura!
Play the flute like you always do!
I wanna hear it!
Actually... the flute is broken.
Aww!
The flute may have broken,
but we still have the Memorin.
Memorin?
It's a shell you can blow
into to store a memory.
You can do that?
I can hear Lady Yura playing the flute!
Please stay here for the night.
I have business to attend to,
so I will return to the castle.
Yori, Mio, take care of the rest.
Of course.
This way, please.
We'll see you later, Yura-san.
Damn it! Damn it all!
What shall I do to that damned Yura?
Zodon!
You're late! What have you been doing?!
Get over here and help me
already, you dullard!
Z-Zodon...
How dare you?!
Damn it... Damn it... Damn it!
How could a low-born
like you do this to me?!
You will not get away with this!
What?
The only dullard here is you.
- Go on.
- Huh?
You're worried, aren't you?
Th... Thank you!
What's the matter with Gobta?
Nothing at all.
Ever since I was little, I've lived
for the good of my kingdom... my people.
To see smiles on everyone's
faces brought me joy.
But sometimes...
it's too much, even for me.
At times like those, I'd sneak
out here to look at the stars.
Stars?
Ever since we were
entrusted with the flute,
the people of my clan have
prayed for Kaien's sake.
The messenger told our ancestors
that if they continued to pray
to the Great Water Dragon,
it would grant them a place
to live under the sea.
The Great Water Dragon was sustained
by the people's wishes and prayers.
But then the people saying
the prayers began to quarrel,
until they all disappeared.
The ancestors accepted its offer and
gained its permission to live here.
The Great Water Dragon then fell
into a long slumber,
and the people of Kaien
continued praying to it.
As priestesses, it has always been
my clan's duty to offer those prayers
in the form of a song on the flute.
But now the flute...
and the Great Water Dragon...
I can't be like this.
I'm sorry you had to see me
in such a pathetic state.
You're not pathetic.
Huh?
We Goblins used to be super weak.
But then we met Great Rimuru,
and since then, we've fought by his side.
Our enemies from
that time are our friends now,
and we all built a nation
of our own together.
The people of Kaien are our allies.
I'll help out, too.
And you'll have Great Rimuru helping you!
So it's gonna be fine!
Thank you, Gobta.
This sure is a nice place.
The food was delicious, as well.
Yeah, it was.
I hope Gobta was able to see her.
I should be heading back.
Everyone... will be worried.
I've come to collect you,
Priestess of the Water Dragon, Yura.
Zodon?!
- Ow!
- Yura!
You're just a Goblin.
Gobta!
Know your place!
Stubborn little insect.
Go feed yourself to the sharks!
Gobta!
Great Rimuru! Great Rimuru!
Great Rimuru!
Yori and Mio?
What's wrong?
It's Lady Yura!
Lady Yura hasn't returned!
Yura-san? But Gobta
just went to find her...
Great Rimuru?!
Master, look!
Gobta!
G-Great Rimuru...
Yura... Yura's in trouble!
Are Yori and Mio safe?
Is Djeese behind this, too?
Djeese...
That man was useless.
A fool who didn't realize I was lending
him my strength and guiding him.
What are you saying?
Also, I have not touched your attendants.
It was a lie to get you to accompany me.
Why did you bring me here?
What are you going to do?
I am going to marry you.
You will be my wife, Yura!
If you and I are together,
we could rule the whole world.
It will all belong to me.
Your body, your soul,
your powers... everything.
My powers?
What power could I possibly have now?
The one I need the most: you yourself.
Yes, the only one who can bring out
the hidden power sleeping deep within you
is me, your husband!
There's no reason to fight it.
Now, just relax and give yourself to me.
Wh-What is this sensation?
No... I can feel...
the Great Water Dragon next to me?
That can't be!
Wh-What was that?
The Great Water Dragon's memory?
It just looked so much like Yura...
I see. That's right.
I...
The search party is ready. We'll send—
Notice.
There is a powerful energy response
coming from the sea floor in Kaien.
The Water Dragon?!
- Yura?!
- Zodon?!
So Zodon was behind all this?
The Water Dragon is revived.
But the flute was broken.
The power to communicate with
the Water Dragon comes not from the flute,
but from Yura herself.
Yura has become my wife.
I will keep her by my side
and take care of her...
so that I can rule this world
for all eternity!
What was that?!
Notice. Kaien has begun to move.
What?!
Wh-What?
What's going on?
The chains are going to...
What is that?
It's... not nuclear magic, is it?
Huh? What?
Uh, isn't this really bad?
It would seem so.
That is the light of the
Water Dragon's demise.
Let's go!
Great Rimuru!
Where's the Water Dragon?
There.
It's heading for the island!
I guess I have to try.
Beelzebub!
Did he get it?!
Notice. I have determined that
only seawater was swallowed.
Seawater?
Great Rimuru, look!
It turned into the Water Dragon?!
This is the power of the Water Dragon!
All of the water
in the ocean becomes its body.
So long as this ocean exists,
it can never die.
Man, are you serious?
Not even a Demon Lord can
dry up an entire ocean.
If you did that, the whole
world would be destroyed.
He is an even more
troublesome foe than I thought.
Rejoice, you trash of Kaien.
I will allow all of you to die for me!
Become a part of the Water Dragon!
Calm down!
Please remain calm!
Kaien has begun to ascend.
What?!
Get all of the people to shelter!
Sire!
Hurry!
Please move quickly!
Ramiris!
Can you move them to the labyrinth?
Don't be ridiculous!
There are conditions to be met,
and they're not being met!
Not as tough as it looks!
Begone! Melt Slash!
With me, Gobta!
You got it!
No! They're heading your way!
I see it.
Leave things here to me.
- Let's get going, Treyni!
- Right!
Beretta!
Yes, Lady Ramiris.
Too slow!
Arcane Thread Shredder!
Evaporate!
Hell Flare!
Thirty-four!
Thirty-five down!
Let us go, my wife.
What's that?
It's Yura!
How in the...
Give Yura back!
Gobta?!
Wait for me, Yura!
Gob—
Yura!
Gobta!
Well done, my wife! My Water Dragon!
A Demon Lord is nothing to fear!
What intense power...
Yura...
You're kidding!
If it's not one thing, it's another!
What's going on?
Yura, your blood and
flesh all belong to me.
Become one with me.
Wha?!
Yura, your power is now at my command.
Let us become gods together.
The island?
Starting with that island...
I will be the supreme ruler
of the whole world.
A... song?
Yura...
It's Yura's song...
Gobta!
Ranga! We have to go save Yura!
Call me
Gobta!
Notice.
I sense waves caused
by the individual called Yura.
What?!
There is a high possibility
that the individual
Slow down
there's no need to rush just yet
called Zodon has erected
a special barrier.
Good call
break through the blue that leaves me breathless
Back me up!
Right!
I've been holding it in,
emotions tangled, stuck in this mess
Did I not tell you
to behave yourself, my wife?
Searching for a place
where my sinking thoughts can rest
I hear your voice screaming my name
Yura!
- Ranga!
- Right!
Crushing up against your weakest side
Transform!
If I raise my sharpened fists
it's okay to get hurt
I already know what strength is
When the time comes, I'll be ready
Before it all disappears, I swore
I'd protect you
Don't break me, I'll live with you
Following the dazzling light as it guides me
Tracing a scene where our worlds collide
Fill this impulsive desire to coexist
With a harmony only we can create
Enduring pain, I'll keep singing
Almost there!
Our silhouettes etched in the melody
Yura!
If this chaos sheds light on the truth
Gobta...
let it make us face reality
I want to stop this runaway spiral
Yura, you should sleep a bit longer.
I'm not going down
A world made for just
the two of us will soon be complete.
Crushing up against your weakest side
I hear her!
If I raise my sharpened fists
Over there!
it's okay to get hurt
I already know what strength is
When the time comes, I'll be ready
Before it all disappears, I swore
Please get there in time, Gobta!
On my way!
I'd protect you
Don't break me, I'll live with you
Go!
Yura!
Yura... I love you!
Gobta!
Get away from Yura!
Crushing up against your weakest side
If I raise my sharpened fists
it's okay to get hurt
I already know what strength is
When the time comes, I'll be ready
Before it all disappears, I swore
There you are!
I'd protect you
Megiddo Ray!
Don't break me, I'll live with you
Following the dazzling light as it guides me
Tracing a scene where our worlds collide
Fill this impulsive desire to coexist
With a harmony only we can create
Notice.
All of the Water Dragon's
waves have disappeared.
Okay...
Where's Gobta?!
Gobta!
Megiddo Ray, eh?
Rimuru...
just how much calculation did that take?
We'll have to arrange
a delicious breakfast for everyone.
Rimuru, Gobta...
Thank you.
The nation of Kaien has been saved.
What happened to
the Water Dragon in the end?
This time... it is truly gone.
Yura...
Yura.
I love you.
If...
If you'll allow me...
I'd like to stay in Kaien.
I want to stay here and help you...
and live out my life with you.
Don't get ahead of yourself.
I am grateful to you,
but I have no feelings
for you beyond that.
I'm sure we will establish diplomatic
relations with Tempest and other nations.
I was only using you for that purpose.
I never had any intention
of living with you.
Yura...
Gobta...
Next time, don't be misled
by an evil woman like me.
Yura!
Yura...
It didn't work out!
A woman's heart is deeper
than the ocean, I guess.
These things happen.
Great Rimuru...
That's right, Gobta.
When things happen,
just lean on Great Rimuru!
There she goes speaking for me again!
Huh...
Hey! Don't look at me like that!
I'll always follow you!
Whoa, wait, wait!
It'll be fine.
You're Great Rimuru, after all!
There's something I wanna ask right away!
Uh, just hang on a minute...
Now that we no longer have
the Great Water Dragon,
many hardships will
surely befall our nation.
We must guide our people
with the support of the priestesses.
Yes, sire!
Where is Yura? Why isn't she here?
Lady Yura...
She isn't even shackled by her
bloodline anymore, and yet...
She simply refuses to show herself.
Please see to Kaien's future.
Thank you. That's enough.
I'm sorry, Gobta.
You see, at that moment...
I knew everything.
My clan has always been taught
that we received the flute
from the Great Water Dragon's messenger.
But that's wrong.
I myself am the Water Dragon's core.
I have been reborn over
and over for generations.
I'm sorry, Gobta.
What you said...
truly did make me happy.
I hope... to see you again.
Notice. The presence of the individual
called Yura has disappeared.
I see...
Yura will come back, though.
You knew?
I just had a hunch.
Past two in the morning, the journey begins
Along a hazy route, deep into you
Words swallowed beyond the swirling darkness
Rocking gently, filling my lungs
My heart beating like an SOS
propagating amidst the raging waves
Would it be okay to try layering it?
Come over here
It sure is painful, it sure is scary
But I sure feel the urge to live
Let me dwell in your warm sea, bathed in light
Just smile, and be angry
Go ahead, you can cry and scream all you want
The helm of your own story lies in your hands
Days drifting aimlessly, endlessly
Dawn is near, I tell myself, gripping the oar
Blown by the sea breeze, scooping up tomorrow
There's value in setting out to row
I want to believe
I can believe
With you, to the utopia we wish to reach
We who are incomplete, and the sky that remains black
Fear not of them, and slumber to the sound of the ship
When you awaken, the spell will be broken
The morning glows softly, like a lamp being lit
Listen to me
Should you wish
Should you pray
Just say it out loud
Like the azure blue of a newborn child
Just scream it out, just resist
That is what it means to live
Raise your face
and set sail into the dawn sky
Let's take each other's hands
Night melts away into the distant sky
A flock of birds takes flight, circling round and round
Have you at last learned your place?
I will come for you again.
Complete the preparations by then.
And I suggest you correct
that impertinent attitude of yours.
A slime Demon Lord?
That could be more fun
than playing with Leon.
You lost, huh?
I didn't lose!
There's always next time.
I said I didn't lose!
Looks like I won't have to
be bored much longer.
(End)